Tony Tran

Los Angeles, CA (858) 216-6128 tran.tony.08@gmail.com **Full-Stack Developer**

Portfolio GitHub LinkedIn

Full-Stack Developer with one year of experience in software development and with also three years of experience in the geology field with fieldwork, remote sensing, ArcGIS, and geologic map making. Experienced coordinating in teams to efficiently build projects such as a Pomodoro Timer and ThinkfulCupid as well as independently working to develop individual projects such as a Decoder Ring and The Flashcard-o-Matic.

Skills

Front-End: JavaScript ES6, React, React Hooks, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap

Back-End: Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Knex

Additional: Mocha, Chai, Git, GitHub, Heroku, Vercel, RESTful APIs, Unit testing, C++

Projects

Decoder Ring | Project Link

- Designed an app that encrypts and decrypts strings through Caesar Shift, Polybius Square, and Substitution Cipher; tested with self-written unit tests to ensure proper functionality and operation.
- Built with: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Mocha, Chai.

Flashcard-o-Matic | Project Link

- Created an app that receives and stores user inputs of flashcards and displays flashcards on a functional, user-friendly interface.
- Designed with a dozen component files using methods such as useEffect, useState, and event-listeners.
- Built with: JavaScript ES6, React, React Hooks, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap.

WeLoveMovies | Project Link

- Developed an app that displays movies, movies reviews, and theater locations following a RESTful API back-end architecture.
- Built with: JavaScript ES6, Express, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Knex.

Experience

Postmates/UberEats

Driver

Los Angeles, CA

October 2020 - Present

- Completed over 1,000 customer pickups and deliveries on the UberEats and Postmates platform.
- Received high remarks with a 99% customer satisfaction rating and praise for timeliness, efficiency, excellent friendly service, and handing off at pickup and drop-off points correctly.
- Self-employed, manage maintenance of vehicles, manage financial bookkeeping and miscellaneous operations to maintain high quality of service.

Barista Los Angeles, CA

UCLA, School of Engineering and Applied Sciences (SEAS) Cafe

August 2018 - March 2020

- Worked with a team to open the facility, close the facility, maintain excellent customer service and manage upkeep of the student café.
- Qualified for manager position, distinguished employee of the month four times.

Education

Certificate of Completion, Software Engineering Immersion

Remote

 Gained teamwork, independent, and computer logic skills necessary to work in a production software engineering environment.

 Highly intensive full-time program covering Front-End and Back-End necessities such as JavaScript, PostgreSQL, HTML5, CSS3.

B.S., Geology

Thinkful

Los Angeles, CA

University of California, Los Angeles

September 2016 - Present

Expected December 2021

 Conducted several field research studies using Hi-res imagery and ArcGIS including the analysis of the Rainbow Basin terrain NE of Barstow, CA and the Isotopic Oxygen Gradient Zone along the North American and Pacific tectonic plate boundary in Eastern San Diego and Imperial Counties of California.